[{"answer": "Fame in itself is an addictive drug and also fame creates an image which you cannot live up to.", "docId": "120214pmt", "aSentId": 6, "question": "Plus was Whitney's fame simply too much for her to bear?", "qSentId": 5}, {"answer": "I did, Piers.", "docId": "120214pmt", "aSentId": 30, "question": "What did he tell you?", "qSentId": 29}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120214pmt", "aSentId": 39, "question": "Another thing that he wanted to talk about that I asked him about, you know, that whole thing, Piers, about Mickey Fine, the pharmacist that was involved with the Michael Jackson case?", "qSentId": 38}, {"answer": "EMON: Yes.", "docId": "120214pmt", "aSentId": 56, "question": "What do you know about that?", "qSentId": 55}, {"answer": "Fans being robbed.", "docId": "120214pmt", "aSentId": 76, "question": "What were you reacting to?", "qSentId": 75}, {"answer": "I mean that's -- I mean she gave the fans something, she gave them her amazing music, her amazing voice through her records that will be there forever, the best performances of all time.", "docId": "120214pmt", "aSentId": 80, "question": "Do you think there is any duty if you have a star of the magnitude of a Whitney Houston to give the fans something though?", "qSentId": 79}, {"answer": "I heard it Saturday.", "docId": "120214pmt", "aSentId": 85, "question": "When did you hear the news of Whitney's death?", "qSentId": 84}, {"answer": "You know, I wasn't around her all the time.", "docId": "120214pmt", "aSentId": 102, "question": "What do you think -- knowing her as you do, what do you think?", "qSentId": 101}, {"answer": "I mean, you know, when I've seen her, she's always really a very up person, she's so full of life.", "docId": "120214pmt", "aSentId": 114, "question": "How did she seem to you, Whitney?", "qSentId": 113}, {"answer": "Is it right to apportion any blame or do you think --", "docId": "120214pmt", "aSentId": 163, "question": "I'm sorry?", "qSentId": 162}, {"answer": "You know I have a feeling that she did what she wanted to do, you know, in working with her.", "docId": "120214pmt", "aSentId": 192, "question": "And Chaka Khan -- could you imagine that she just would instinctively rail against anyone that tried to tell her what to do?", "qSentId": 191}, {"answer": "You know, it wasn't -- I mean, it was weird, yes.", "docId": "120214pmt", "aSentId": 203, "question": "What did you feel?", "qSentId": 202}, {"answer": "HOPRA: It's a very complex issue, Piers.", "docId": "120214pmt", "aSentId": 240, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 239}, {"answer": "So I don't see a lot of -- I don't usually hang out with a lot of the artists I work with, so I don't see a lot of that.", "docId": "120214pmt", "aSentId": 262, "question": "I mean when they become fabulously famous, rich, successful, and they start getting into this whole drug scene, illegal and legal, do you see a change in them?", "qSentId": 261}, {"answer": "You have to realize, first of all, that fame actually causes the same brain chemical changes as a drug does.", "docId": "120214pmt", "aSentId": 318, "question": "How do you treat an addiction to fame?", "qSentId": 317}, {"answer": "Piers, I'm not at liberty to talk about that right now.", "docId": "120214pmt", "aSentId": 327, "question": "How is she doing?", "qSentId": 326}, {"answer": "I think that any singer that sings as amazing as she sung, when you have a certain pain that you can touch people, that you're carrying a pain with you.", "docId": "120214pmt", "aSentId": 359, "question": "When you worked with her, were you aware of all these struggles she was going through?", "qSentId": 358}, {"answer": "She obviously led a very tortured life.", "docId": "120214pmt", "aSentId": 375, "question": "What went wrong?", "qSentId": 374}, {"answer": "To take some direction, but, you know, you can't have conversations with people when they're stars about certain things.", "docId": "120214pmt", "aSentId": 413, "question": "But her instinctive reaction would be to rail against whatever you wanted?", "qSentId": 412}, {"answer": "I think she was vulnerable.", "docId": "120214pmt", "aSentId": 428, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 427}, {"answer": "We talked about it later, when -- the first time I visited her at her house.", "docId": "120214pmt", "aSentId": 452, "question": "How did she react to that afterwards?", "qSentId": 451}, {"answer": "Better than anybody on the planet.", "docId": "120214pmt", "aSentId": 471, "question": "She had -- how good was her voice at its best?", "qSentId": 470}, {"answer": "For me.", "docId": "120214pmt", "aSentId": 473, "question": "Literally?", "qSentId": 472}, {"answer": "I always say she was the best singer ever.", "docId": "120214pmt", "aSentId": 476, "question": "Has there ever been a better recording voice?", "qSentId": 475}, {"answer": "Didn't really talk about it.", "docId": "120214pmt", "aSentId": 503, "question": "Do you know how she felt about it?", "qSentId": 502}, {"answer": "You just made a record.", "docId": "120214pmt", "aSentId": 507, "question": "Was it just like the unmentionable?", "qSentId": 506}, {"answer": "I think so.", "docId": "120214pmt", "aSentId": 529, "question": "Should it be something that we focus on really, or should we celebrate -- and I sort of instinctively am beginning to feel should we focus more on these incredible songs she sang?", "qSentId": 528}, {"answer": "Unfortunately, Iran is running terror against Israel for many, many years.", "docId": "120214pmt", "aSentId": 556, "question": "What is your overview on what's going on here?", "qSentId": 555}, {"answer": "HALOM: Israel is trying to stop the military program of Iran for years.", "docId": "120214pmt", "aSentId": 566, "question": "Would Israel go alone?", "qSentId": 565}, {"answer": "Every one of us, it doesn't matter if you're Israelis, Americans, Europeans, we are in favor of those people that are asking for freedom, for human rights, for liberty.", "docId": "120214pmt", "aSentId": 580, "question": "Has it become a problem for you?", "qSentId": 579}]